Contact

9109208989 (Home) kentuckyhannan@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christopherhannan-a8365382 (LinkedIn) yahoo.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Acute Care
Medical/Surgical
Patient Safety

Christopher Hannan

Travel Nurse at trustaff

Fayetteville, North Carolina

Summary

Experienced Emergency Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing Throughput Management, Disease Management, Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, and Medication Administration. Strong professional with a Associate's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Paducah Community College.

Experience

trustaff

2 years 4 months

Travel Nurse

March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Goldsboro, North Carolina Area

Registered Nurse Emergency Department

March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Cape Fear Valley Health System

9 years 5 months

Charge Nurse

June 2008 - October 2017 (9 years 5 months)

fayetteville area, north carolina

Lead ED Flow Manager

June 2008 - October 2017 (9 years 5 months)

Fayetteville, North Carolina Area

Education

Paducah Community College.

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (1994 - 1997)